

+90 545 294 57 44

- ayberkgerey@gmail.com
- github.com/ayberkgerey
- Pursa/Orhangazi TR

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering

Zonguldak Bulent Ecevit Üniversity

2019 - 2023

Orhangazi Anatolian High Sch. Bursa - Orhangazi 2014 - 2018

EXPERTISE

React Native

React JS

Spring Boot

HTML-CSS-JS

ES6

Responsive Design

LANGUAGE

Turkish - Mother Tongue

English - Fluent Talk, Professional

German - Basic

AYBERK GEREY

Software Engineer

About Me

My greatest will is to learn more about my passion, programming. Since my academic journey started, I have dedicated myself to increase my programming skills. My coursework and my personal projects taught me so many experiences about software development . I have a great ambition to develop apps and making them better. I am always open to learn more and I love communicating with people in this bussines as well.

Experience

2023 Aug- 2023 Oct

P LastGuard

I made fixes in teamwork for the website written with React JS. Added many features and worked on its development.

2021 APR - 2021 AUG

Freightest Inc.

Fixed bugs, added responsive pages, started to make mobile app of company and added so many new features.

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

VirusSafe

Started to make a React Native app for controlling their new air cleaning device.

APR 2019 - AUG 2019

Seismicity Level Project

Worked with a team to build a new android app for Earthquake- safe places in Turkey.

Projects

Formulal Tracking

This is an application I made for myself to track formula 1 stats and information about teams, racers and circuits. Made with React-Native

Cocktailla Recipe

Cocktailla is a React-Native application for users want to make fresh cocktails by themselves at anywhere as long as they have the right ingredients. Live on Google Play

SpaceFlight News

This is a news application for space and space technology enthusiasts. There are several sources to read from all over the world and interact to their websites.

Articles

M1 Apple Silicon And React-Native IOS Build Problems

First Step To Spring Boot

What are those Spring Annotations